<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chine.eu</title>
    <link>https://en.chine.eu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chine.eu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.x-v-france.com/&#34;&gt;X. (more information on X-v-France.com)&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:16:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://en.chine.eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Constitution of the People&#39;s Republic of China</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/laws/constitution-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:16:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/laws/constitution-china/</guid>
      <description>Constitution of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China (Adopted at the Fifth Session of the Fifth National People’s Congress and promulgated by the Announcement of the National People’s Congress on December 4, 1982; amended in accordance with the Amendment to the Constitution of the People’s Republic of China adopted at the First Session of the Seventh National People’s Congress on April 12, 1988, the Amendment to the Constitution of the People’s Republic of China adopted at the First Session of the Eighth National People’s Congress on March 29, 1993, the Amendment to the Constitution of the People’s Republic of China adopted at the Second Session of the Ninth National People’s Congress on March 15, 1999, the Amendment to the Constitution of the People’s Republic of China adopted at the Second Session of the Tenth National People’s Congress on March 14, 2004, and the Amendment to the Constitution of the People’s Republic of China adopted at the First Session of the Thirteenth National People’s Congress on March 11, 2018)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sūn Qiáng (孙强)</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/persons/sun-qiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 15:32:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/persons/sun-qiang/</guid>
      <description>Full name: Sūn Qiáng (孙强). Position: director (captain). Badge number 015865. Police station: Gulou police station, Taiyuan, Shanxi province.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wáng Chén (王晨)</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/persons/wang-chen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 23:07:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/persons/wang-chen/</guid>
      <description>Full name: Wáng Chén (王晨). Position: 二中队民警. Badge number 014075. Police station: Miàoqián police station, Taiyuan, Shanxi province.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminal law</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/laws/criminal-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 13:28:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/laws/criminal-law/</guid>
      <description>Criminal Law of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China
Adopted by the Second Session of the Fifth National People&amp;rsquo;s Congress on July 1, 1979 and amended by the Fifth Session of the Eighth National People&amp;rsquo;s Congress on March 14, 1997
Part I General Provisions
Chapter I Tasks, Basic Principles, and Scope of Application of the Criminal Law
Article 1. This law is formulated in accordance with the Constitution and in light of the concrete experience of China launching a struggle against crime and the realities in the country, with a view to punishing crime and protecting the people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chén Liàng (陈亮)</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/persons/chen-liang/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 21:23:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/persons/chen-liang/</guid>
      <description>Full name: Chén Liàng (陈亮). Position: director (captain). Badge number 014590. Police station: Longtan police station, Taiyuan, Shanxi province.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hú Zhēn (胡珍)</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/persons/hu-zhen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 21:23:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/persons/hu-zhen/</guid>
      <description>Nom complet: Hú Zhēn (胡珍) Position: Political commissar. Badge number 016428. Police station: Longtan police station, Taiyuan, Shanxi province.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wáng Xiàoqí (王孝其)</title>
      <link>https://en.chine.eu/persons/wang-xiaoqi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 21:23:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.chine.eu/persons/wang-xiaoqi/</guid>
      <description>Full name: Wáng Xiàoqí (王孝其). Position: deputy director (deputy captain). Badge number 016424. Police station: Longtan police station, Taiyuan, Shanxi province.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
