<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Laws on ECTHRwatch</title>
    <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Laws on ECTHRwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.x-v-france.com/&#34;&gt;X. (X-v-France.com)&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Directive 2005/29/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11 May 2005</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/directive_2005_29_ec_of_the_european_parliament_and_of_the_council_of_11_may_2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 11:23:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/directive_2005_29_ec_of_the_european_parliament_and_of_the_council_of_11_may_2005/</guid>
      <description>Directive 2005/29/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 11 May 2005</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Guidelines for Victim and Witness Assistance</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/attorney-general-guidelines-for-victim-and-witness-assistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/attorney-general-guidelines-for-victim-and-witness-assistance/</guid>
      <description>Foreword to the Attorney General Guidelines for Victim and Witness Assistance (2011 ed.) “Our core mission is to pursue justice for criminal acts, and that pursuit includes justice for the victims of and witnesses to crime. Every day, Department personnel encounter individuals harmed by crime or who witnessed others being harmed by crime. How we treat those individuals has a huge impact on their confidence in the criminal justice system and their ability to heal and recover from crime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Corrupt Practices Act of 1977</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/foreign-corrupt-practices-act-of-1977/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/foreign-corrupt-practices-act-of-1977/</guid>
      <description>Introduction “The Foreign Corrupt Practices Act of 1977 (FCPA) (15 U.S.C. § 78dd-1, et seq.) is a United States federal law that prohibits U.S. citizens and entities from bribing foreign government officials to benefit their business interests.”
“The FCPA is applicable worldwide and extends specifically to publicly traded companies and their personnel, including officers, directors, employees, shareholders, and agents. Following amendments made in 1998, the Act also applies to foreign firms and persons who, either directly or through intermediaries, help facilitate or carry out corrupt payments in U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FBI Victim Assistance Program</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/fbi-victim-assistance-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/fbi-victim-assistance-program/</guid>
      <description>Source: FBI Victims of Crime brochure
The FBI’s Commitment to Victims of Crime Each year, the FBI investigates thousands of crimes involving hundreds of thousands of victims, including many child victims. These crimes result in great harm to individuals, families, and communities. Individuals impacted by crime face the daunting task of rebuilding and healing from loss while navigating the criminal justice system.
Federal laws protect victims of Federal crime and provide them with a voice during the investigation and prosecution of their case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COUNCIL DIRECTIVE 93/13/EEC of 5 April 1993 on unfair terms in consumer contracts</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/council_directive_93_13_eec_of_5_april_1993_on_unfair_terms_in_consumer_contracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 11:23:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/council_directive_93_13_eec_of_5_april_1993_on_unfair_terms_in_consumer_contracts/</guid>
      <description>“Whereas contracts should be drafted in plain, intelligible language, the consumer should actually be given an opportunity to examine all the terms and, if in doubt, the interpretation most favourable to the consumer should prevail;”
“Whereas Member States should ensure that unfair terms are not used in contracts concluded with consumers by a seller or supplier and that if, nevertheless, such terms are so used, they will not bind the consumer, and the contract will continue to bind the parties upon those terms if it is capable of continuing in existence without the unfair provisions;”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article 313-1 of the French Criminal Code</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/french_criminal_code_article_313-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 11:23:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/french_criminal_code_article_313-1/</guid>
      <description>“Fraud is the act, either by the use of a false name or of a false designation, or by the abuse of a true quality, or by the use of fraudulent maneuvers, of deceiving a physical or judicial person and thus to determine, to its prejudice or to the prejudice of a third party, to deliver funds, values or any good, to provide a service or to consent to an act operating obligation or discharge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
