<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rights of Federal Crime Victims on ECTHRwatch</title>
    <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rights of Federal Crime Victims on ECTHRwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.x-v-france.com/&#34;&gt;X. (X-v-France.com)&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 14:07:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FBI brochure regarding the FBI Victim Services</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/fbi-brochure-for-fbi-victim-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 23:02:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/fbi-brochure-for-fbi-victim-services/</guid>
      <description>FBI Victim Services (brochure from the FBI, 2018) (source: FBI.gov).
Click on this link to visualize the original document: fbi-victim-services-brochure-2018.pdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Attorney General Guidelines for Victim and Witness Assistance 2022 Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/attorney-general-guidelines-for-victim-and-witness-assistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 14:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/attorney-general-guidelines-for-victim-and-witness-assistance/</guid>
      <description>The Attorney General Guidelines for Victim and Witness Assistance 2022 Edition) (source: Justice.gov).
Click on this link to visualize the original document: ag_guidlines_for_vwa_2022_edition.pdf
Page 5, D. Privacy Considerations for Victims and Witnesses:
“Department personnel have a responsibility to protect the privacy of victims and witnesses, including their personally identifiable information (PII) and other sensitive information. This responsibility aligns with a victim’s right to be treated with fairness and with respect for the victim’s dignity and privacy, which is a broad-based right that should be applied in all contacts with victims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FBI brochure regarding the rights of victims of financial crimes</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/fbi-brochure-for-victims-of-financial-crimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 15:19:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/documentation/rights_of_federal_crime_victims/fbi-brochure-for-victims-of-financial-crimes/</guid>
      <description>Financial Crime and You (brochure from the FBI, 2018) (source: FBI.gov).
Click on this link to visualize the original document: vsd-financial-crime-and-you-brochure-2018.pdf
“How Will I Obtain Information? Federal crime victims have a number of rights dur- ing their participation in the criminal justice system, including the right to limited information about the status of the case.”
“Some victims have losses so severe that they are unable to meet current financial obligations.”
“Many victims feel anger, resentment, frustration, shame, embarrassment, and guilt, as well as fear for financial security and personal safety.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
