<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Witness protection on ECTHRwatch</title>
    <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/tags/witness-protection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Witness protection on ECTHRwatch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.x-v-france.com/&#34;&gt;X. (X-v-France.com)&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ecthrwatch.org/tags/witness-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Guidelines for Victim and Witness Assistance</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/attorney-general-guidelines-for-victim-and-witness-assistance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/attorney-general-guidelines-for-victim-and-witness-assistance/</guid>
      <description>Foreword to the Attorney General Guidelines for Victim and Witness Assistance (2011 ed.) “Our core mission is to pursue justice for criminal acts, and that pursuit includes justice for the victims of and witnesses to crime. Every day, Department personnel encounter individuals harmed by crime or who witnessed others being harmed by crime. How we treat those individuals has a huge impact on their confidence in the criminal justice system and their ability to heal and recover from crime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FBI Victim Assistance Program</title>
      <link>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/fbi-victim-assistance-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 11:21:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ecthrwatch.org/laws/fbi-victim-assistance-program/</guid>
      <description>Source: FBI Victims of Crime brochure
The FBI’s Commitment to Victims of Crime Each year, the FBI investigates thousands of crimes involving hundreds of thousands of victims, including many child victims. These crimes result in great harm to individuals, families, and communities. Individuals impacted by crime face the daunting task of rebuilding and healing from loss while navigating the criminal justice system.
Federal laws protect victims of Federal crime and provide them with a voice during the investigation and prosecution of their case.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
