<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>X. on Carine Smith Ihenacho (non-official)</title>
    <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/authors/x/</link>
    <description>Recent content in X. on Carine Smith Ihenacho (non-official)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/&#34;&gt;Home&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/about-me/&#34;&gt;About me&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/contact-me/&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/copyright-and-disclaimer/&#34;&gt;Copyright and disclaimer&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/privacy/&#34;&gt;Privacy&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ecthrwatch.org/other-websites/&#34;&gt;Other websites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Non-official&lt;/i&gt; website on Carine Smith Ihenacho, NBIM’s Chief Governance and Compliance Officer&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.NBIMwatch.org&#34;&gt;Norges Bank Investment Management Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.Nicolai-Tangen.com&#34;&gt;Nicolai-Tangen.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i&gt;non-official&lt;/i&gt; website on NBIM’s CEO&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.Trond-Grande.com&#34;&gt;Trond-Grande.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i&gt;non-official&lt;/i&gt; website on NBIM’s Deputy CEO and Chief of Staff&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://Dag-Huse.NBIMwatch.org&#34;&gt;Dag-Huse.NBIMwatch.org&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i&gt;non-official&lt;/i&gt; website on NBIM’s Chief Risk Officer&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ECtHRwatch.org&#34;&gt;European Court of Human Rights Watch&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:12:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/authors/x/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chris Kempczinski, CEO of McDonald’s Corporation, is asked if Kevin Ozan’s departure is related to the criminal RICO case targeting them.</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/chris-kempczinski-asked-if-kevin-ozan-departure-is-related-to-the-criminal-rico-case-targeting-mcdonalds-corporation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/chris-kempczinski-asked-if-kevin-ozan-departure-is-related-to-the-criminal-rico-case-targeting-mcdonalds-corporation/</guid>
      <description>Click this link to see the original LinkedIn post.
Dear Mr. Kempczinski,
Is Mr. Ozan’s departure related to the criminal RICO case targeting McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Corporation and if yes, to which extent is it related? (look at the screenshot 👇 to understand)
You also mention Mr. Ozan’s “unwavering integrity,” could you please confirm he reported internally my stern warnings about the crimes McDonald’s is engaging into?
As the CFO, he obviously should have understood McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Corporation is engaging in money laundering, shouldn&amp;rsquo;t he?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicolai Tangen and NBIM’s executives asked who is the anti-money laundering officer at Norges Bank Investment Management</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/nicolai-tangen-and-nbim-executives-asked-who-is-nbim-anti-money-laundering-officer-2023-05-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:29:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/nicolai-tangen-and-nbim-executives-asked-who-is-nbim-anti-money-laundering-officer-2023-05-02/</guid>
      <description>From: X. (Anonymity granted by decision of the Court)
Date sent: May 2, 2023, 15:29 (Beijing time)
Cc: Nicolai Tangen (CEO of NBIM)
Cc: Ida Wolden Bache (Governor of Norges Bank), Trond Grande (Deputy CEO of NBIM), Carine Smith Ihenacho (NBIM), Dag Huse (CRO of NBIM)
Open letter/communication, submitted via a LinkedIn post, to Nicolai Tangen, CEO of Norges Bank Investment Management corporation, and CC&amp;rsquo;ed to various executives and the @FBI, in reply to his LinkedIn post whether “Can you spot the dragon?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trond Grande and Dag Huse are asked about Carine Smith Ihenacho’s email address</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/trond-grande-and-dag-huse-asked-about-carine-smith-ihenacho-email-address-2023-04-06/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 23:43:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/trond-grande-and-dag-huse-asked-about-carine-smith-ihenacho-email-address-2023-04-06/</guid>
      <description>From: X. (Anonymity granted by decision of the Court)
Subject: Email address of the Chief Compliance Officer Ms. Carine Smith Ihenacho
Date sent: April 6, 2023, 23:43 (Beijing time)
To: Trond Grande (Deputy CEO of NBIM), Dag Huse (CRO of NBIM)
Dear Messrs. Grande and Huse,
My name is [REDACTED FOR PRIVACY (note: but I of course gave them my real name)]. I attach a scan of my expired passport and my current Chinese driver’s license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunger Strike. Reply from French Law Professor Yves Strickler</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/2019-01-04_1957_0800_email_from_strickler/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 19:57:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/2019-01-04_1957_0800_email_from_strickler/</guid>
      <description>Note: this email has been redacted for brevity. Check the French version of this page for the full content.
Key point: French law professor Yves Strickler didn&amp;rsquo;t disapprove the possibility for me to do a hunger strike to protest the repeated violations of my fundamental rights by France. For the record, I am now accusing McDonald’s of having corrupted French officials. It might help to explain why McDonald’s France and McDonald’s Corporation, and their accomplices, have never been indicted for serious fraud and money laundering in France.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additional frauds; email sent to McDonald’s General Counsel CCed to McDonald’s CEO</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/2015-10-22_1106_0800_additional_frauds_email_to_santona_cc_easterbrook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 11:06:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/2015-10-22_1106_0800_additional_frauds_email_to_santona_cc_easterbrook/</guid>
      <description>From: X. (Anonymity granted by decision of the Court)
Subject: additional frauds
Date sent: 2015-10-22 11:06 (Beijing time +0800)
To: Gloria Santona &amp;lt;Gloria.Santona@us.mcd.com&amp;gt; Cc: Steve Easterbrook
Ms Santona,
Thank you for answering me. Could you please make sure the French team communicate with me by email? Normal mail takes forever for me to receive now that I live in China and I am not going to wait one month to act if there is an ongoing fraud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4th formal notice sent to the executives of McDonald’s Corporation to keep warning them that McDonald’s France has engaged in a pattern of racketeering activity</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/mcdonalds-executives-formally-notified-of-ongoing-serious-frauds-in-europe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 12:01:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/mcdonalds-executives-formally-notified-of-ongoing-serious-frauds-in-europe/</guid>
      <description>From: X. (Anonymity granted by decision of the Court) Subject: Translation of yesterday&amp;rsquo;s email Date sent: October 21, 2015, 12:01 (Beijing time) To: Gloria Santona &amp;lt;Gloria.Santona@us.mcd.com&amp;gt; Cc: Steve Easterbrook, Robert Gibbs (Robert.Gibbs@us.mcd.com), Silvia Lagnado (Silvia.Lagnado@us.mcd.com), Kevin Ozan &amp;lt;Kevin.Ozan@us.mcd.com&amp;gt;, Jim Sappington (Jim.Sappington@us.mcd.com), Mike Andres &amp;lt;Mike.Andres@us.mcd.com&amp;gt; PLEASE FIND HERE THE TRANSLATION OF THE EMAIL I SENT YOU YESTERDAY. Mesdames, Messieurs, Dear Sir or Madam, Je vous ordonne de faire cesser immédia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“I sold my soul to McDonald’s”</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/i-sold-my-soul-to-mcdonalds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2013 12:12:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/i-sold-my-soul-to-mcdonalds/</guid>
      <description>This book contains a crucial evidence that McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Corporation executives could have easily, through a simple phone call, stop the ongoing frauds which were happening in France, and later in Europe.
Then, why didn&amp;rsquo;t they?
In addition to the fact that there is an undeniable proof that, contrarily to what Gloria Santona said, this was a French problem, the book offers additional insights about how McDonald&amp;rsquo;s seems to corrupt politicians.
To gain a clearer understanding of the sequence of events in this case, I invite you to view a detailed timeline at the following link:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Françoise de Borda, former general counsel of McDonald’s France</title>
      <link>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/reply-from-francoise-de-borda-general-counsel-mcdonalds-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 13:13:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carine-smith-ihenacho.nbimwatch.org/open-letters/reply-from-francoise-de-borda-general-counsel-mcdonalds-france/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Via certified mail with proof of receipt requested&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From: 
 
  
  
 
 
 
 Françoise de Borda (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Francoise.deBorda@fr.mcd.com&#34;&gt;Francoise.deBorda@fr.mcd.com&lt;/a&gt;)
To: 
 
  
  
 
 
 
 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.x-v-france.com&#34;&gt;X. (Anonymity granted by decision of the Court)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I recall correctly, a copy of the mail was sent to a French Ministerial Officer who I now accuse of being corrupted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Translation coming soon. (Note of 2023-04-13: quick note, this event happened in 2012 and I published it, if I am not mistaken, on 2022-09-21T20:49:00+08:00. Back then I wrote “translation coming soon” but I currently don&amp;rsquo;t have time to translate what was said in French. It&amp;rsquo;s an important event but not that important compared to what I am currently explaining to the FBI which is the priority.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Françoise de Borda, directrice juridique de McDonald’s France, me réponds pour la première et pour la dernière fois. Elle ment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
